foxpush.com 2019-06-07

# Privacy Policy | Foxpush Free Website Push Notifications

Effective date: 5/25/2018, last edit: 05/25/2018

Please review our Privacy Policy, which is part of our Terms and Conditions. The Privacy Policy describes how we collect and handle any information gathered from users of the Services. By accessing or using the Service, including browsing the site, you expressly consent to the collection, use, storage, processing, and disclosure of your information in accordance with our Privacy Policy. 

For purposes of this Policy, unless otherwise defined herein, capitalised terms used in this Policy shall have the same meaning as defined in the Terms and Conditions. 

  * #### Introduction

FoxPush, LLC. Privacy Policy contains information about collecting Customers, Visitors and other data subjects (like Clients or End-users) Personal Data and other information, products and Services offered or performed by FoxPush, LLC. and the manner of its processing. We respect the right to privacy of our software users and take reasonable steps for the Visitors and Customers to be familiar with the manner in which rendered accessible information via the following websites www.foxpsuh.com and support.foxpush.com is processed. Due to the implementation of comprehensive security regulations, Personal Data provided by our Services and websites is of highest security standards. The acceptance of Terms and Conditions for the use of any FoxPush, LLC. Services or deciding on using or purchasing any Service offered by FoxPush, LLC. means accepting FoxPush, LLC.. Privacy Policy. 

FoxPush, LLC complies with the EU’s GDPR and constantly work on improving our internal process to insure the protection and security of our Customer and End-users data. 

  * #### Scope

This Privacy Policy is effective to all information collected by FoxPush, LLC. from which an individual can be identified (Personal Information/Personal Data). This Privacy Policy also applies to all Personal Data received by FoxPush, LLC. in the EEA (European Economic Area).

  * #### Compliance with Law

Please be aware we may disclose Personal Data to respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. We may also disclose Personal Information if it is necessary in order to prevent, investigate or take action regarding illegal activities, or as otherwise required by law. 

  * #### Questions and concerns

If you have any questions or concerns, or if you wish to access, update, amend, correct or delete, any of your Personal Information we store and process, please contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

  * #### What information we collect

    1. Provided Data:  
The scope and purpose of gathering and processing Personal Data and other information by FoxPush, LLC. is: 
      * to provide, maintain and facilitate the Services as well as to ensure safe and guaranteed Service performance, upgrade and improve the functionality of the Services,

      * to provide Customer with access to its Personal Data and maintain this access via FoxPush’s Dashboard interface for the duration of the usage of Services (active subscription) as well as after the subscription is expired (inactive subscription), until the Service is fully terminated by a written request (in accordance with the Agreement), 

      * to secure (establish, investigate or defend) Customer’s, as well as Company’s claims that may arise due to the Services, 

      * to stay connected with the Customer to present up-to-date offer of Services and instructions or tips related to the Service. 
    2. Personal Data and other Customers information collected by FoxPush, LLC. is used in order to complete registration (create an account) and at the same time to ensure Customers access to FoxPush, LLC.’s Services. While registering to our website (www.foxpush.com), we request that you provide us with such information as: first name, last name, company business name, address, website address, e-mail address and credit/payment card information in the event when a Customer decide to move to one of FoxPush’s paid plans. If the Customer decides to use our Services under our free plan, credit/payment card information is not required. We also collect other information provided by Customer while using our Services. Some of the provided Customers information such as: your IP address, domain, browser type, operating system type etc. may be automatically acquired when a user visits our websites. When contacting FoxPush, LLC. the Customer may be requested to render accessible analogical data to those provided while registering on our website. 

    3. Personal Data provided in connection with the correspondence between the visitors and FoxPush’s, LLC. Customers using FoxPush, LLC’s “Lead Generation feature”. These personal data shall be used strictly to reply to the visitors inquiries. When using the support section of our sites we may collect your e-mail address, name or openID account for the purpose of allowing contact with our support team. We do it regardless you are a Visitor or a Customer. When using our Services we may collect device information such as device type, operating system type and application version. We use this information in order to provide an optimized version of our product for your device type. Please be aware we also collect and process data related to the use of our software and Services by our Customers and their customers. We use such data for statistics purposes. We may use it also to improve our Services or create and improve new services. We collect and process such data collectively and anonymously. 

    4. Types of Customer Personal Data   
The proceeded personal data includes email address, first name and last name, address, title, contact details, username, chat history, financial information (credit card details, account details, payment information); employment details (employer, job title) and other data in an electronic form provided in the context of the Services. 
    5. Consent for processing and transferring Personal Data The Customer agrees and warrants that the processing, including the transfer of its Personal Data has been and will continue to be carried out in accordance with the relevant provisions of the applicable Data Protection Laws (and, where applicable, has been notified to the relevant authorities of the Member State where the Company is established or has its representative) and does not violate the relevant provisions of that State.

    6. Return or destruction of Personal Data. At Customer’s election, made by written request to the Company, the Company will, and shall procure that all Sub-processors: 

      * return a complete copy of all Customers Personal Data to the Customer.
      * and delete and procure the deletion of the Customers Personal Data Processed by the Company or any Sub-processor. The Company will comply with any such written request within 30 days, unless it is unworkable due to the purposes of processing or due to the technical issues. 
    7. Retention of Copies. The Company may retain Customer Personal Data to the extent required by applicable European Union law or the law of an EU Member State and only to the extent and for such period as required by such laws and always provided that the Company shall ensure the confidentiality of all such Customer Personal Data and shall ensure that such Personal Data is only processed as necessary for the purpose(s) specified in such law requiring its storage and for no other purpose. The Customer agrees that after the termination or expiration of the Agreement its data may be stored as a backup for the time needed to secure (establish, investigate or defend) Customer’s and Company’s claims that may arise due to the performance of the Services (for the time it takes for the claims to be barred). 

    8. Geo-Location databr   
Please be aware FoxPush, LLC. may have access to your geo-location data as we collect and process IP address of all devices you use our software on. Collecting and processing your geo-location data refers to mobile devices as well as computers. Geo location data is limited to the Country and City of the end-user. 
    9. Communications from the site   
We will occasionally send you push notifications in order to make you aware of any outages of Service. You may opt-out of receiving these types of communications by turning off push notifications at the device level. If you wish not to receive such notification you have an option to ‘unsubscribe’ this type of communication anytime. We will also send you notifications related to some important updates of our Services. The purpose of sending you such e-mails or messages is to keep you informed of the latest improvements, features and other developments. 
    10. Third party Personal Data   
We allow you to provide us with third party Personal Data. We mean End-users data (your visitors/customers, people who uses Services to contact you). The information that we may collect is first name, last name, e-mail address and other contact information. We do it in order to allow you to send personalized web push notifications to your end-users who opted to receive such notification from your behalf. We will not use this information for any purpose which is not compliant with our Privacy Policy. Please be aware we process Personal Data of your End-users. We will not use this data for any purpose which is not compliant with our Privacy Policy. 
    11. Children personal data   
We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from anyone under the age of 13. If you notice we collect and process Personal Data of anyone under the age 13 incorrectly, please contact us at: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children’s Internet usage and to help enforce this Policy by instructing their children never to provide Personal Information through the websites or Services. 
    12. Cookies 

Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer's hard drive. We place cookies in end user’s and customer’s browser to identify the user. Cookies do not contain any of your personally identifiable information. If you do not wish FoxPush to capture any of your non identifiable/anonymized information You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service. 

  * #### Data Disclosure

    1. FoxPush, LLC.’s main purpose of gathering Personal Data and other information is to maintain Services, ensure safe and guaranteed Services performance for its Customers, upgrade and improve functionality of its Services. Owing to the above process we exceed our Customers’ expectations, we provide a constant development of our Services the use of which becomes much easier and more convenient. In order to ensure orderly and safety functioning our Service we cooperate an use a software of other entities providing services (described below). We do not sell or lease, your Personal Data to any third party. We will never share, sell rent or trade your registration and Personal Information with any marketing or promotional partners without your consent.  The following are exceptions, with respect to whom we may share your Personal Information: 

      * FoxPush, LLC. reserves the right to disclose Personal Data to any of our parent, subsidiary, affiliated or successor companies. 
      * a. FoxPush, LLC. reserves the right to disclose and the Customer agrees for the disclosure and transfer its Personal Data and other information relating to the Customer to Third Party Service Provider (including Sub-processors) such as hosting, credit card processing. On your request we can provide you with a list of entities which may have access to your Personal Data. We ensure these entities have access only to the minimum part of the Personal Data which is necessary for the proper service provision. 
      * FoxPush, LLC. shall observe due diligence to make sure the processing of data disclosed to any entities is in compliance with our Privacy Policy and the currently effective law. 
      * Credit/payment card data provided by the Customer are disclosed solely to professional companies that conduct non-cash transactions and only to the extent necessary to effect the payments. Except for the above situations FoxPush, LLC. shall not disclose any information or personal data provided by Customer. 
      * Personal Data can be disclosed to entities into which our company is merged, or to which our assets, site or operations have been transferred. Mentioned entities will be able to use your Personal Information under the terms of this Privacy Policy. We will notify you if any of these events occur by updating this Privacy Policy and, if practically possible, via other means. 
    2. Personal Data and other information provided by Customer shall not be disclosed to third parties unless the obligation to disclose the information to third parties results from the currently effective provisions of law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process, when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request, or if it is necessary for the FoxPush, LLC’s security and its rights protection, including the protection against the claims submitted by the third parties. The provided Customer’s information may be utilized in the event of breach of Terms and Conditions for the use of Services, misuse of funds, the necessity to take action against all Customer’s unlawful actions. FoxPush, LLC. shall transfer no information or Personal Data to any third parties for marketing purposes. FoxPush, LLC. reserves the right to use the provided Personal Data for the marketing purposes and other purposes connected with presenting up-to-date offer of Services and instructions or tips related to the Service in direct contacts with the Customer. You may opt-out from such e-mails at any time by following the unsubscribe instructions located at the bottom of each communication. 

  * #### Choice

You may request details of the Personal Data that we hold about you. You have the choice to restrict our collection or use of your Personal Data in the following ways : 

    1. When you are asked by us to accept a cookie or to fill in a form on the Website, look for your cookie settings and the area that you can click to indicate your preference as to use of your Personal Data for marketing or other purposes; and 
    2. If you have previously agreed to accept a cookie, then you may change your mind at any time disabling or deleting the cookie or amending your cookie settings. 
  * #### Security

We guarantee that we take reasonable and appropriate technical and operational measures to protect your Personal Information we collect and hold from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction. While protecting your personal data we take into due account the risk involved in the processing and the nature of the Personal Data. 

  * #### Access

Each data subject has the right to access, correct, amend, block or delete its Personal Data. The Company shall comply with any commercially reasonable request by Customer to correct, amend, block or delete Customer’s Personal Data, as required by Data Protection Laws, to the extent the Company is legally permitted to do so. If you wish to access, amend, or confirm that FoxPush, LLC. has Personal Data relating to you, or if you wish to correct or delete your Personal Information if it is inaccurate, please notify us at: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) You can also easily remove your data from our data base by simply unsubscribing from notifications. Upon unsubscription, all data is removed from our database. For More information on how End-users can unsubscribe from receiving notifications from a specific website and deleting their personal data you can find information on support.foxpush.com. 

  * #### Recourse, Enforcement and Liability

Since we are committed to protecting your privacy as set forth in this Policy, if you think we are not in compliance with our Policy, or if you have any question or if you wish to take any other action concerning this Policy or your Personal Information, we encourage you to contact us. We will investigate your complaint, take appropriate action and report back to you within 30 days. 

  * #### Data Protection

FoxPush, LLC. applies technical safety measures of the highest standards to protect the provided Personal Data against loss, destruction, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure. The used measures and technology ensure complete safety of the Personal Data provided by the Customer. The Personal Data is available solely to the Customer or to a person indicated by him provided authorized access has been granted to that person.The security of your Personal Data is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal data submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. FoxPush, LLC. takes all necessary steps to update and modernize data protection system. No data transmission via the Internet, however, can guarantee 100% safety. 

  * ####  Privacy Policy modification 

We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any significant material changes we will notify you by e-mail (sent to the e-mail address specified in your ‘owner’s account’) or by means of a notice on the website prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this website for the latest information on our privacy practices. 

  * #### Terms and Conditions

Using offered Services rendered by FoxPush, LLC. the Visitor and the Customer are obliged to comply with rules contained in the Terms and Conditions available on our websites
